kurdland.com 2008-12-17

# Kurdland.com - kurdistan kurds kurdish music mp3 midi kurdish links email voice chat java text chat kurdishmusic voicechat textchat toplist poll news postcards ecards poetry subdomains links free ringtones mobile muzikikurdi muzik midifiles download song gorani ringtones mobile wap books ebook pdf files wallpaper news iran iraq turkey syria dating contact date kurdish woman women girls boys men marriage love meet single singles kurdishmusic kurdi kurd domain subdomain webhosting webhotel webspace

|  |    
 |   
  
---|---  
  
|  **Startpage** |  **Submit link** |  **World News** |  **Postcards** |  **Music** |  **Video** |  **Downloads** |  **Member pages** |  **The Toplist** |  **Most visited sites**  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  

|  |  |  | **Privacy Statement for Kurdland.com**  
|   
---|---|---  
|  |    

**Privacy Statement for Kurdland.com  
** Kurdland.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Kurdland.com.  
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don´ t see the same ad repeatedly.We USE cookies TO SAVE your password so you don´t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.  
This site contains links to other sites. **Kurdland.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.  
 **  
Public Forums  
** This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  
 **  
Security  
** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  
 **  
Supplementation Information  
** This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.  
 **  
Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.  
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.  
* You can send email to our [**webmaster**](http://en.kurdland.com/contact.asp) **

Correct/Update

** This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.  
* Using our contact [**form**](http://en.kurdland.com/contact.asp)

|   
---|---|---  
|  |   
  
|  |  |  |  | **Add your link**  
|   
---|---|---  
  
|  |   

|  | Contact us |   | Make Kurdland to your startpage |   | Add Kurdland to your favourites |   | Privacy Statement |   | Tell a friend about Kurdland |   | Poll  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
© 1998-2008 Kurdland. All rights reserved.
